seoforlocalbusinesses.com 2011-12-25

# SEO for Local Businesses: Privacy Policy

**General Privacy Policies**

We respect your interest in your privacy and as a result we have created this  
informational disclosure. 

We collect and use personal information for many purposes, including but not  
limited to, billing; product and service fulfillment; to better understand our  
customer needs; to provide a better website, products and services; to communicate  
with customers and potential customers regarding our products and services and  
third party products and services. 

Generally, your private information will only be disclosed to our owners, employees,  
independent contractors, subsidiaries, partners, affiliates, attorneys, consultants,  
business associates, service providers, suppliers and agents, acting on our behalf  
or request. This general rule, and disclosures in specific situations, is more  
particularly described below. 

You must be at least 18 years old to access this website. We do not direct this  
website to persons under 18, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information  
from children under the age of thirteen.

**Information Collected by our ISP**

The hosting provider for this Internet site (as with any Internet site) has the  
ability to record various information, including domain name, pages accessed,  
date and time of access, web browser type and computer operating system, and  
referring information, and to disclose this information. This is most commonly  
done by providing access to raw server logs. For more information you should  
perform an Internet search on ‘server logs’ or ‘raw server logs.’ We may have  
access to our raw server logs and access reports prepared by our hosting provider.  
**Financial Information for Billing Purposes**

We sell products and services. When sales are made financial information must be  
disclosed. This information can include any number of facts you are asked to provide,  
but most commonly includes your name, financial / credit card information, billing  
address, and email address. Generally, this purchase information will be provided by  
you to a third party payment processor and we do not receive your financial / credit  
card information. 

In the event we do receive financial / credit card information, we will not disclose  
it to anyone unless disclosure is required by law or a court order, or unless disclosure  
is required to address an issue implicated by the financial transaction. If you claim  
that your financial information was used to make a purchase you did not authorize, details  
about the financial transaction may be disclosed to law enforcement and anyone else we deem  
necessary to address the matter. 

**Use of**

An important part of our services includes being able to provide information to you. As a  
result, you expressly consent to receiving communications from us via email, fax, telephone,  
mail, or any other delivery method. 

As a customer you are agreeing to receive information about the product or service you  
purchased.  
This may include, but is not limited to, information about product or service updates, new  
features, or information we believe you may find interesting.  
We may also send you information about other products and services our company offers. 

We will not sell, provide, or transfer you email address to others. 

We may allow advertising to our customers, or engage in joint ventures, which result in  
your receiving advertisements from selected third parties.  
**Identification of Purchasers**

If you purchase one of our products or services, you authorize us to use your name and  
identification information in advertising or promotions.  
We also use personal information in an aggregate form (i.e., not individually attributable  
to you) for business analysis, operational, marketing and other promotional purposes.  
**Cookies**

Cookies may be used to keep track of referred affiliate commissions and to monitor access to  
our website. You consent to any future use of cookies for testing purposes and the use of  
cookies for publicly available data to gather statistics for the purpose of determining  
which search engines, referring sites, key words, etc., bring visitors to our website,  
which pages visitors are most interested in, what web browsers are used, etc. Various  
providers may be used for this purpose. The purpose is obtain information  
that will help promote the website, make the website more interesting and useful to  
visitors, and to identify areas where improvement is needed.  
Additionally, various third party information suppliers and other entities that provide  
information for this website, or for use by us, may use cookies. Examples include, but  
are not necessarily limited to billing providers, third party advertisers, and third  
party resources we promote.

**Disclosure by Necessity**

Private information may be disclosed if required by a court order, statute, law, or  
regulation.  
Information is subject to disclosure to address a claim that you are violating the  
terms of any agreement pertaining to your use of your use this website or our products  
or services, or rights of any third party.  
Information is also subject to disclosure if we believe that disclosure is necessary to  
identify, contact or bring an action against someone who may be causing injury to or  
interfering (either intentionally or unintentionally) with our rights or property, your  
rights or property, other users of our website, products or services, or anyone else.  
As we continue to develop our business, we or our affiliates may sell or buy other  
businesses or entities, or we may merge with another company, or be bought by another  
company. In such transactions, personal information may be one of the transferred assets.  
Your information may be stored and processed in any country in which we maintain facilities  
or conduct operations. By using our website, products and services, you consent to any such  
transfer of information outside of your country.  
After your account becomes inactive your information may remain in our databases, computers,  
and archives, and cannot reasonably be expunged.  
**Policy Changes**

These policies may be amended by us at any time and without notice, but will be posted at  
this page.  
You agree that your continued use of our websites, product or service after that date will  
constitute your consent and acceptance of the amendment.  
Effective Date: Immediate
